Jl. Sadar II RT 1 RW 3 No.20 Larangan, Ciledug, 15153 +62-8213-9810-9027 | +62-8129-1617-011

About Me

Experienced and Driven Software Developer with Impressive Background of Building such robust App, Library, and Framework. Worked with team in good attitude to handling the tasks and managing the quality of work to achieve the optimal System quality. Experienced working as Penetration Testing to audit the weakness, vulnerability and whole security of the System based on malicious tools as same as nowadays hacker in legitimate manner and lawful ways.



Experiences

Global Sukses Digital — Software Developer	2020 — Now
Global sukses digital which is commonly called DOSS is the biggest retail store camera and gadget located in Jakarta and had multiple branches in every province in Indonesia. My role here to solved and built robust system that can integrate with 3 rd party microservices such as logistics, accounting, and more.	
Bfi — Software Developer	2020 — 2020
BFI is startup company that moving in Data science. A lot of chart that BFI create for researcher. My role at BFI is just software developer. Creating tools for researcher such as social media and more using python and php.	
Lawgo — Backend Software Developer	2020 — 2020
Working at lawgo as part-timer software developer. In lawgo we working together to bring lawyer and people can be connected as easy as possible. Using PHP laravel in the backend but mostly	

my role is to connect realtime activity such as chat, notification even "call request like" using	
Google firebase services, such as cloud functions, cloud messaging, and realtime database.	
Ertri Indonesia — Web developer	2019 — 2020
Ertri is one of the biggest digital agencies in indonesia, thousands of big clients that use our	
services. As web developer I have to responsible to build web app and web game for clients using	
Lumen, Uikit, MySQL and Godot Engine to create such minimal or robust web.	
Eidara Matadata Presisi — Digital Analyst & Software Developer	2019 — 2020
Worked as Digital Analyst and Software Developer in Eidara Matadata Presisi to solved the	
problem in agriculture, urbanism and civil infrastructure. We use UAV (unmanned aerial vehicle) to	
ease our project and also digitizing the image into 3D and a lot translation to help our veteran	
and expertise in their work field. And also using Machine Learning technology with <i>Firebase, Flask,</i>	
Tensorflow and Open drone map to simplify the work.	
Indowebdeveloper — Lead Software Developer	2016 — 2019
Decreasible and coff	
Responsible as Lead Software Developer Team in Indowebdeveloper to manage the team tasks	
what's priority or small issue. Fully responsible from Systems Design, Analytic the Requirement,	
and Create the Milestone for team, and also Working to design core of the best practice for	
system so the team could work together in harmony. a lot project we've done in	
Indowebdeveloper from the smallest project to the enterprise. In Indowebdeveloper we using	
PHP with Laravel, AngularJS, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, and Also MySQL as our core development	
tools or language.	
Qasico — Core Software Developer	2015 — 2016
Qasico is start-up company that focused in Integrated Business Application, became part of Core	
Software Developer in Qasico is quite challenging and fun. Responsible to create Library, tools,	
and Helper for team Software Developer to ease their work. Also Design the System with the	
team how it should be worked and how it should be running. In gasico we basically use <i>PHP with</i>	
Laravel, AngularJS, MySQL, Go as API, Java and Python as our development tools and language.	
Cakra Manunggal Pratama — Software Developer	2013 — 2015
Worked as Full Stack Developer in Cakara Manuggal Pratama to solved the environment problem	
with System. Focused in building System that can be used to minimalize the cost impact of office	
production and also providing the training of ISO-9001. In Cakara Manunggal Pratama we've	
basically using <i>PHP with Codelgniter, Jquery, MySQL</i> and <i>Java</i> as our core development language.	
GMF Aeroasia — IT Helper	2011 — 2012
Givi Acrousiu — II ricipei	2011 — 2012
As Intern in GMF Aeroasia. Responsible to maintain and monitoring the activity of the network,	
building the network router with mikrotik, and also helping the client in technical problem so they	
can continue their activity.	

Publication and Works

Kommand

Kommand is open-source library for python to gather, documented and execute function directly with Command Line/Terminal.

The library is already available on PvPI.

Bandingin.com

Bandingin.com is an enterprise website that we've build in Indowebdeveloper, bandingin is tech company for users to find any insurance that's suits for them We build bandingin.com using complex mathematical algorithm to ease the users find what kind of insurance are suits for them based on price, feature, popularity, and average.

Membangun Applikasi Android dengan Python Kivy

An Article in CodePolitan to Introducing a new Natural User Interface (NUI) framework written using Python. This article contains the easiest way how to create android app using kivy-python.

Stigma | Gunion - Flexible and Expressive Python Framework

Stigma or what is now known as Gunion is small project in <u>GitHub</u> to create almost anything, such as 2D games, android apps or just common apps. The architecture is almost same as web development because it's inspired from Django and Laravel architecture system. The update still on going in GitHub and planned to bring it further. The <u>Demo of 2D game</u> build on it is in the GitHub as well.

Assets Management System for Cakra Manunggal Pratama

A small project that we've created in Cakra Manunggal Pratama to ease our work in manage our assets, using PHP with Codelgniter as backend system this project is worked and already been sold in other company that might actually needed

FeedR - Mini RSS Reader App with PHP

FeedR is Small RSS Reader written using PHP, using PHP native without any framework FeedR could fetch any RSS in all website that provide it. FeedR is available in sourceforge.net

Skills

Python	Along with Django, TensorFlow, ODM, Flask, and Kivy	
Google Services	Firebase, Cloud, and Suite	
Elasticsearch		
JavaScript	Along with AngularJS, Socket.io and Redis	
С		
Java	Along with Spring	
PHP	Along with Codelgniter, Laravel, Fuel PHP, Phalcon and Symfony	
Linux	Familiar with almost all Linux such as Kali, Slackware, CentOS and Arch	
SQL and No SQL	Familiar with SQL such as MySQL, PostgreSQL, and SQLite. For NoSQL is MongoDB	
Penetration Testing	Experienced exploiting with Metasploit, Sniffing, Web Exploit and Reverse Engineering.	

Certification

CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associated)	2012
CCINA (CISCO CEITITIEU NETWORK ASSOCIATEU)	2012

Education

Telkom school shandy putra jakarta 2013